(Howard:)We are going
to Meh-he-co!
Fun, I've never been there!
Leonard, don't be fooled!
(Sheldon:)I'm from Texas...
Meh-he-co is Spanish for Mexico.
(Raj:)What's wrong with Mexico?
(Sheldon:)Uh, mariachi bands, wild dogs,
(Sheldon:)beans that jump around
'cause there's a worm inside.
(Howard:)Okay, calm down.
(Howard:)There's a theme
to this weekend.
(Howard:)We are going to Mexico
in Feynman's van
(Howard:)to stay at the vacation house
Feynman bought
(Howard:)with the money
from his Nobel Prize.
Viva la Imodium!
Ay-ay-ay!
(Bernadette:)Come on, Leonard's
doing bachelor stuff.
(Bernadette:)You sure we can't take
you to a strip club?
(Penny:)Nah, if I want to see
a naked dancing man,
(Penny:)I just flush the toilet
while Leonard's in the shower.
(giggles)
(Sheldon:)Hi.
Hey.
(Amy:)I know we're not making a fuss,
(Amy:)but in the spirit
of bachelorette parties,
(Amy:)I made cookies in the
shape of male genitals.